<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome on Seely Street Bed and Breakfast</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Welcome on Seely Street Bed and Breakfast</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fundy View Room</title>
      <link>/rooms/fundy_view_room/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/rooms/fundy_view_room/</guid>
      <description>Fundy View Room
We just love this room and this is our most popular room with our repeat visitors. The Fundy View room is spacious with vibrant colours creating a warm relaxing atmosphere, ideal for a romantic break or a long weekend away from the hustle and bustle of life. Welcome to our new feature room with lovely views over Seely Street and looking towards the Bay of Fundy with Mispec and Red Head in the distance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Deer View Room</title>
      <link>/rooms/deer_view_room/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/rooms/deer_view_room/</guid>
      <description>The Deer View Room
Many times we have watched the deer in our rear gardens from this room as they wander between the houses on their way from Rockwood Park. This large bedroom room in the middle of the house offers a Private Bathroom and a walk-in closet with a Queen Sleigh Bed. There is a large dresser and mirror and a great old fireplace. We think of this room as one in which to relax and unwind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Seely Suite</title>
      <link>/rooms/seely_suite/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/rooms/seely_suite/</guid>
      <description>The Seely Suite
Tucked away at the rear of our house is our Private Suite with bedroom with Queen Bed, separate sitting room and en-suite bathroom. This is a great room for long stays as you have the comfort of a living area as well as privacy due to its location in the house. We have a Sofa Bed in this room so that we can accommodate a family of 4 or 4 adults in 2 double beds.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
